「チェーンジェイル」 これは　お前達 「クモ」にしか使わない力
I have to defeat him, or it's all over!
「幻影旅団」を捕らえ その自由を奪う そのためだけに使うと 誓った力
I'll do whatever it takes to protect Gon!
確かに…　奴らか？
Yes! That's more like it! That terrified expression...
クラピカ　もっと飛ばすぞ 追っ手だ！ 追っ手!?　誰が？　まさか…。
Damn, I'm getting excited now...
糸！　恐らく「念」の！
I'm gonna tear you apart.
クソっ！
I have to protect him... I have to...
あっ　バレた。 案外　早かったね。
When you know nothing of your opponent... ...protect Gon.
大丈夫　もう追いつく。
...run away.
どうでもいいが この狭いの どうにかなんねえのか？
No matter what!
やっぱ　ただ者じゃねえな お前ら。
Is there something special about that tree?
あの一瞬に　ドアを開けて 脱出する反応の鋭さはよ。
Just wait a little longer.
へへ…。
They're only found around brackish water, and this is their breeding season.
こりゃまた大勢で。
It's beautiful! Isn't it?
どうかした？ 「陰獣」って　全部で１０人だよね？
You piss yourself or something?
さっき　ウボォーが倒したのが ４人だから
Well?!
これで全部　揃ったことになる。
Can't even move a muscle? Lose your spine?
じゃあ　鎖の使い手は 「陰獣」じゃないってこと？ まぁ　こいつらに聞けば分かるね。
Damn, this feels so good... Should I kill him?
全部　生かしておくの？ いや　生かしておくのは 梟って奴だけでいい。
Ah, but I want to enjoy this!
「陰獣」の恐ろしさを教えてやるよ。 …だってさ。
Here.
シャルナークは そこで見てなね。
It's a present.
私が３人　シズクが２人ね。 分かった。
This is the most beautiful flower in the world.
落ち着け！　奴らの力を侮るな！
It is?
うるせぇ！
Stay still.
筋弛緩ガスと睡眠ガスを 用意させるって。 効いてくれるといいが…。
The tree's sap is very similar to
the pheromones fireflies emit, so they tend to gather around branches.
動くと切れるよ。
I'm so happy...
あっ　あぁ…。
Thank you. Really?
はい　終わり これ　どうする？
I'm glad to hear that.
ほっとくね 今さら隠しても意味ないね。
But I...
さてと　拷問にかける前に
I can't give you what you truly want.
ノブナガを風呂敷から 出してもらおうか。 ちょっと待って。 ん？
What I truly want?
この　梟とかいう奴も 車に乗せるんだろ？
Time alone with me. Eh?
私も狭いの嫌だなぁ。
I want to become stronger.
ねぇ　車だけ風呂敷から 出すことって　できるの？
Strong enough to defeat the Chimera Ants.
マジで　キレるぞ！ 不可能だ…。 残念。 しょうがないか。
That means I have to train harder.
どうなってんだ！
In two days, Kite's coming back.
てめぇら！　この！ よくも遊んでくれたな！
To return him to normal, I'll probably
have to fight whoever is controlling him.
団員同士のマジギレ禁止。 黙れ！ それにしても 私達の仕事には便利な力ね。
So until Kite is back to normal...
うっせぇ！ こいつは俺様　切り刻む！
Or if possible, until the
Chimera Ants are defeated...
ダメね　そいつには持ち去った お宝の在りかを話してもらうね。
I want to focus on my training.
君も　とことん運がないね。
Yes... Yes!
あ…　うぅ…。 チクショ！
Are you okay with that?
おい　起きろ！
Huh?
盗んだ競売品を　どこにやった？
Gon!
立場が分かっていないようだ…。
Because
質問は 俺がするんだ！
we're friends...
うっ！ うぅ！ あぁ…。
You're my dear friend!
何という精神力
Stop that...
明らかに　これから拷問を 受けることが分かっていながら
Don't look at me like that.
体をまとうオーラには わずかな動揺も見られない
I c-can't stop myself...
こいつの 頑強な肉体を支えているのは
I'll kill you. I'll kill you! I'll kill you...
不動の精神力
Run.
それによって つくられるオーラは
Shut up!
まさに　百戦錬磨
Run.
俺がするんだ！
Shut up!
あぁ…。 何という精神力
I'll leave the head, but eat the rest! Run.
明らかに　これから拷問を 受けることが分かっていながら
I don't want
体をまとうオーラには わずかな動揺も見られない
to lose him! Run.
こいつの 頑強な肉体を支えているのは
Gon is...
不動の精神力
Run.
それによって つくられるオーラは
...my...
まさに　百戦錬磨
Run. ...dear...
体は…
Run.
ダメだ 回復に 相当　時間が　かかりそうだ
It has to be Killua.
夕飯　食ったのが８時頃 腹の具合からみて１２時前後か
My very dear friend!
は？ 命は助けてやるから 今すぐ　これを外せ。
He disappeared?
命ごいしなきゃいけねえのは こいつのほうだろうが。
He fooled me good.
ふぅ…　もう一度だけ言うぜ。
Illumi must have planted this
俺達が欲しいのは 地下の競売品だけだ。
inside my head.
お前らは　その在りかを 知らねえようだから　用はねえ。
Huh? What are you talking about?
あぁ？ ちょっと待って。
Have you lost your mind? And how did you dodge that?
あなた達が取ったんじゃないの？ すでに金庫は空だった。
Wait, I saw the whole thing.
「陰獣」って奴らが 先に持ち去ってたんだ。 おめぇら　末端にゃ 話が通ってなかったみたいだな。
Right before I reached him, he jammed his finger into his own head.
う…。
And then he vanished, before popping up over there.
ウソは　言ってないと思う。
Yeah, I feel so much better now.
さっきの取引も 強がりや　はったりじゃなく…
I'm completely awake now. Or maybe I should say I'm liberated.
ひぃ…。
That's all that happened! Nothing more...
勘違いは誰にでもあるさ。 俺達は まだ何にも取っちゃいねえんだ。
This can't be happening!
だから　こいつを外して
Now I'm the one who's afraid?!
その後のことも 見て見ぬふりしてくれよ。 そうすれば…
I have a message for the other Ants.
命だけは助けてやる。 あ…。
If you come anywhere near us, your lives are over.
地下の競売場にいた客だ。 我々の仲間も　そこにいた　答えろ。
That's bull!
殺した そういう予定だったんでな…。 あ…。 貴様らの勝手な予定で どれだけの命を奪ったんだ！
Then don't bother.
あぁ　地下から奪われた 競売品の在りかは…。
I don't sense any. That means...
拷問の「ご」の字も 始まらないうちに終わったよ。 あぁ　それで…。
What are you doing?! Eh? Can't you tell?
あ　そうだ。
Well, at least he's okay...
今日 人と会う約束してたんだった。
Leave us alone!
This is none of your business!
行って来るよ。
Right back at you, stupid.
ああ　構わない 明日の午後６時までに戻ればな。
Why don't you make yourself scarce?
もちろん。
Why are you injured?
クソ。
I'll injure you some more!
あ…。
I could dodge your knife in my sleep.
ふぅ…。
I was so sure he was dead...
「約束通り　例の場所で」
Wait! I'll kill you!
さっき連絡があった。
You're just making her angrier. Huh? If we ditch her here, we'll never see her again.
コミュニティーの連絡係の部屋を 突き止めたってさ。 こちらは　ノストラードファミリーの ダルツォルネだ。
We just have to call Knuckle and tell
him we'll meet him somewhere else.
競売を襲った賊の１人を 捕まえたので　お渡ししたい。
I'm going back. Do you want to die?
[TEL] 本当か　一体どうやって？ 詳しくは後で。
If you let your guard down, thinking she's not much of a fighter,
she'll stab you in the back!
[TEL]　大したもんだな 「陰獣」でも無理だったのに。
She wouldn't do that. Huh?!
「陰獣」でも無理だった？ [TEL]　ああ　奴らは全滅だ。
Bu— Didn't you see her take that knife to me?
全滅…。
Damn, you're too much!
[TEL]　で　お前らのいる場所は？ よし　分かった。 [TEL] とにかく早く来てくれ。
They're making a fool of me!
筋弛緩ガスは３本分　嗅がせたよ。
Wherever you run to, I will know!
「隠」は使っていないようだな
I'll chase him to the end of
the world and eliminate him! Make a fool of me, will you?!
安心しなよ 今　君と　やる気はない。
Kno—
無駄話は　したくない。
Knov-sama... Where did those boys go?
早速　お前達のことを 聞かせてもらおう。
R-Right...
そうかい？ 僕は無駄話も好きだけど。
They went to the hotel that
has a logo with three circles.
フッ…。
They're at the Triple Circle Hotel.
「クモ」は構成員１３名で その証しは ナンバー入りのクモのタトゥー。
Yeah, we just got a call from them.
メンバーは 突然　入れ替わることがある。
Um, I believe you had planned
to arrive in two days...
入団志望者が在団員を倒せば交代。 それ以外で欠員が出ると 団長がメンバーを補充する。
No, we're on schedule. We'll use the extra two days
to observe those boys, to determine if they're ready to
see Kite in his current state.
活動は　主に盗みと殺しで たまに慈善活動もする。 そこまでは知っている。
But first things first, Palm! Y-Yes? It appears that you used your
power without my permission.
僕も２３年くらい前に ４番の男と交代で入った。 目的は？
I told you to await my orders,
in case of unforeseen events. Yes...
団長と戦うこと。 団長と？　なぜ　そうまでして…。
Your blood is an irreplaceable commodity.
強いからさ。
Irreplaceable?
自分の強さを 試したいということか？
Use it only for me.
さぁね　ただ
Only for Knov-sama...
ゾクゾクするんだよ。
Understood?
団長と戦うことを想像すると。
Y-Yes.
でも　なかなか達成できなくてね。
Knov-sama really is the only one for me!
ガードが堅いんだ。
And why are you dressed like that?
常に最低２人は団長のそばにいる。
Oh! No reason... N-Nothing's going on!
手掛かりすら　つかめなくなる。
Irreplaceable...
そこで　お互いへの結論だが
Then tell her to wait until
Kite's back to normal.
１人では 目的達成が困難だと思わないか？
I did.
何が言いたい？ 団員の能力を教えようか？ 僕が知っているのは ７人だけだがね。
Gon Freecss, age 12, blood type B, forced into a relationship by Palm
Siberia, age 22, blood type A...
僕と組まないか？
and dumped before he knew it.
ご苦労。
Oh! A secret one! Huh? Really?
ああ　こっちだ。
Yeah, you can auction it on
the net for a lot of money.
注射器が体に通らねえから ガスで体をしびれさせてる。
Then you can have it. Not interested.
あ　あ…　あぁ…。
Did something happen? Hmm? Not really.
耳を疑ったぞ お前がさらわれたと聞いた時はな。 フン。
Let's hit the gym.
ギョギョ。 ウボォーの 体の自由を奪ってる毒を吸い出せ。
Oh, I haven't noticed anything.
ギョギョ。
They seem to be doing fine...
はい　おしまい。
But we should continue to observe them. That will give them time to
conclude their business.
ふぅ…。
While Knov and Shoot were observing
the mental state of Gon and Killua...
みんな　起きて！
He's here.
団長に伝えてくれ。 俺は　鎖野郎とケリをつけるまでは 帰れねえとな。
Not bad.
まだ　それを知らない
He's fast.